

# SHAGOTO BHAKAT

Frontend Web, UI/UX and Graphic Designer

# About Me

I am Shagoto Bhakat. I am a Frontend Web Designer with an experience of 7 years. I design all kinds of Website and Software with Reactjs and Nextjs. I also design with Bootstrap, Material UI, Tailwindcss, Chakra-ui, Theme-ui, Ant design and various kinds of Animations. I am currently working as a Web & Graphic designer on an IT company.

- +8801741148841
- shagoto.bhakat@gmail.com
- Dhaka, Bangladesh
- <u>in LinkedIn</u>

# LANGUAGE

- Bangla
- English

# **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

- HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript
- React JS, Next JS, jQuery
- MySQL, Oracle, Firebase
- GitHub, Git
- Designing:

PSD to HTML

Bootstrap

Material UI

**Tailwindcss** 

Ant Design

Adobe XD

Figma

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Illustrator

Adobe Indesign

Webflow and Canva

## **EXPERIENCE**

Frontend Web & Graphic Designer PERFECT GROUP

01/09/2020 - Currently working

Web Designer
Creative IT Institute
01/01/2019 - 31/12/2019

Jamuna Bank limited 01/08/2018 - 30/11/2018

I have experience of working as a freelancer as well.

# **PORTFOLIO**

As a web designer, I have designed few websites which are now on live. The websites are given below

- MY PORTFOLIO WEBSITE
- PERFECT FOOTWEAR LTD.
- TASHDID Printing And Packaging
- JUNAINA Shoe Trading

Some other design which are designed by me

My Work

## **EDUCATION**

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

B.Sc. Computer Science and Engineering (CSE)

2014-2018 CGPA: 3.23 out of 4.00

Rajshahi Model School & College Rajshahi

Higher Secondary Certificate (HSC)

2013 Group : Science GPA: 4.80 out of 5.00

Rajshahi Model School & College Rajshahi

Secondary School Certificate (SSC)

2011 Group: Science GPA: 4.88 out of 5.00

# ACADEMIC PROJECTS

# Restaurant Management System (Web Application)

Online Application for Billing, Food Storage, Book Table, Employee Management

Code Igniter, HTML, PHP, JavaScript, CSS

# Trello Management

Project Management Application
Visual Studio, C#, MySql.

# Hospital Management System

Using the oracle database. This project use for hospital staff, DR & administrative panel

Database

# Scenery of Bangladesh

Using open GL, create scenery of Bangladesh

**Computer Graphics** 

## **THESIS**

# Framework to Deliver Documents in A Secured Way

**Description:** Comparing the existing algorithms for Unstructured Big Data to replace with the newer ones and proposing a new model that reduces overhead

**Domain:** Data Management Systems

# **INTERESTS**

- Music and Singing
- Web
- Travelling
- Show Movie

## PERSONAL DETAILS

Father's Name : Nimai Bhakat

Mother's Name : Roni Rani Bhakat

Date Of Birth: 10 November, 1996

Gender: Male

Marital Status: Married

Nationality: Bangladeshi

NID No : 912 824 9647

Religion : Hindu

➡ Blood Group : O-

Permanent Address: C/O-Holding No 09, Chindipur, Betiapara, Rajshahi, P.O.- G.P.O, P.S.- Rajpara, Dist.-Rajshahi

Present Address: 36, Pioneer Road, Segunbagicha, Dhaka-1000

## **REFERENCES**

# DR. Tabin Hasan

Professor of Science and Technology

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

# MD. Ezazul Islam

Associate Professor of Science and Technology

American International University-Bangladesh (AIUB)

# **DECLARATION**

I am confident that I have the ability to work with proper responsibility on one's own imitative. I will try my best to perform my duties according to the desired satisfaction of the authority.

I am the undersigned, hereby declare that the above information is true and I will be responsible for any wrong information.

#### **SHAGOTO BHAKAT**

Date: